The Life Do-Over Device
Brought to you by: Ko-FI.me/OrangeFlash
Pass it to me!
There!
I want to play too, kick me the ball.
I wanna play too!
It is my turn!
Giant, Suneo...
You're so annoying!
OK, I will kick it to you!
Bring it on!
What are you doing, Nobita? You're so clumsy!
Quickly pass the ball around!
Excuse me, can you kick the ball this way, please?
You can have it back!
Haven't I seen you somewhere before?
But mister, I think this is my first time seeing you.
Hmm.. Maybe I mistook you for someone else?
What are you doing there, Nobita?!
I am coming!
Mister, please give me the ball!
Oh, sorry
What's wrong? Do you know that mister over there?
No, I don't know him. But he asked me has he seen me before?
What a weird mister.
There's a lot of homework...
Speaking of which, Nobita why don't you improve your football skills?
Well....
It's Shizuka-chan!
Practicing for Soccer match, guys?
We're done for today and are about to head home.
Shizuka-chan, where are you going to?
Cram School.
Cram School?
You're such a study girl, Shizuka-chan!
Not really. Why don't you guys join my cram school as well?
I don't like studying.
I have a tutor at home.
We don't really need cram schools, unlike Nobita, that is.
Tch!
Even Suneo has tough times once in a while.
I'm home!
We have guests?
Oh, is that so?
What a nice kid!
Hi, big bro!
Nobita, come on, say hello.
Make yourself at home.
I can write alphabets, you see.
So smart, show me then...
You have brought your stationery kit, huh? What a thoughtful boy!
How ridiculous!
OK, I wrote my name.
You can write Kanji? How great!
Though he can only write his name for now.
But any preschooler can write, it ain't such a big deal.
But Toshio-chan just turned 5 year old, right?
5 years old?
I can write my name too.
Of course, you are 5th grader.
Toshio is a wonder child!
There are 8 cookies on the desk.
4 people can share 2 pieces each among them.
Wow, you can calculate as well. What a smart little boy!
I challenge you!
Know 13 + 26? = 39
5x5=25, 15x2=30
Then 1/6th of x is...
Nobita!
Enough, get out!
Mum, you're exaggerating that little boy's achievements...
What he can, I can too..
Yeah, sure. But you are a 5th grader...
But a 5-year old boy being able to do that. He's too smart for his age.
5-years old and 5th grader, seriously, who cares? We're both 5!
Well, being mocked by Giant and Suneo outdoors...
And being compared to a 5 year boy at home...
Man, wish I could become 5 years old again...
but with my intellect intact.
Oh! Yes, you can!
I can?
You can become a 5-year old boy again.
Really?
The Life Do-Over Device!
Everyone has moments in their life that they wish they could do over.
Sure.
This device lets you go back and relive those moments differently..
With my present physical strength and intellect intact?
Yes, of course! So that you won't make the same mistakes.
Alright! I'll re-do my life.
I'm gonna live the life of my dreams!
Nobita-kun's present age: 11 years.
To what age do you wanna go back to?
5-years old, of course.
There!
Would using this machine hurt me physically?
No, I don't think so...
Really?
If you are worried, then maybe don't.
No, I wanna do it!
OK, here goes!
He's gone!
What is this place?
What was I doing here?
I've been here before, but...
Now I remember, this was the lumberyard...
...in the neighborhood where I used to play.
I've shrunk and I don't need glasses neither.
Great, I am 5-year old again!
I used to play here all the time! This really takes me back!
Hey, Nobita!
What are ya doin' up there!?
Hide and seek's no fun if you don't look for us!
You're so boring!
Shizuka-chan!
Giant and Suneo!
What's up?
You're all so cute!
Don't Call me cute!
It didn't hurt!
So Giant was violent even at this time.
Takeshi-san, stop, you mustn't bully on a weak person.
Hmph!
Shizuka-chan was very kind to me.
Wimpy Nobita!
Right!
Slowpoke Nobita!
Enough!
So they made fun of me even at this early!
Let's play some fun game.
Let's play the school game.
OK, I will be the teacher.
But I should be the teacher.
i'll, I can write kanji.
I can write too, it's no big deal!
Let's see!
Ok, let's all write Kanji.
OK.
Well.
I wonder what's so fun in this...?
Done.
You wrote Suneo in reverse.
Mine is correct
Shizuka-chan is so smart!
Mine is done!
What's written here?
Is that even a word?
Don't laugh!
Right, write down your name, let us see.
Sure!
My name is ..
Nobita-chan, you can write kanji?
But of course, It is so simple!
Liar, you can't!
Right, you made it up!
But it's real Kanji.
You're a cheat!
Really.
We'll know who's right after we show it to an adult.
I'll bring here that mister over there.
Mister!
What can I do for you?
We'd like for you to read something.
Nobi Nobita, is it a name of someone you know?
He's correct.
What's the matter?
You wrote it ?
Unbelievable.
So that was a real Kanji!
Nobita, can you write something else?
Of course.
Spring, Summer, Fall and Winter.
Mountains, streams, woods..
Nobita-kun, have you did any special classes?
Nope.
What a Genius!
I won't accept that!
I agree with Suneo!
I'll beat you up!
It seems Nobi-chan was again made to cry.
He's a crybaby.
Don't cry, Nobita.
You are boy, remember?
Auntie, you have got it all wrong.
Nobita?
He made them cry?
But I just pushed them!
They started crying...
Nobita, stop being violent.
It is the first time I hear such complaints.
The boys play out together and sometimes violence breaks out.
Excuse me.
Yes, I am coming.
Here's my business card.
The researcher of Education of gifted children
I have come today for Nobita-kun...
I'm astonished that he's just a 5-year old and...
He can already read and write kanji.
But he has just started studying Hiragana.
Then he learned to write by himself?
My Nobi-chan wrote it?
How elegant it looks!
Mother-in-law, have you taught him writing secretly?
Never did!
He can write a lot of words
1 should write more.
OK.
He can write so many!
No way!
Let's do some other test!
Nobita-kun, please answer the following question.
There are 3 Apples, and 3 Bananas, so how many fruits are there in total?
Simple!
6!
Ask a harder question.
Then, 35+13=?
48!
No way!
Unbelievable!
Tell me I'm not dreaming?
I can recite the multiplicaation table
2 x 1 = 2
2x2=4
2x3=6
2x4=8, 2x5=10, 2x6=12
How great it feels to already know everything beforehand!
To tell you the truth, I am quite astonished myself.
I tested him in various fields.
It's hard to believe that he's just 5 years old.
You mean?
I mean your child is a genius!
His intellect is on the same level with a primary schooler.
Great!
5 years old, with the same intellect as a primary schooler.
Yes, I'm a primary schooler in the body of 5 years old.
He's at least on the level of 2nd grade primary schooler.
I actually am a 5th grader.
Really?
Right, he passed the test.
Smart, Nobita.
Thank god,!
He is sure to get into Tokyo University.
He doesn't have to go to cram school.
I wonder if he'll be a professor or a minster, any of them could do.
Oh my, Nobi-chan! Do you wanna go pee?
You can go by yourself?
That's so considerate of you, Nobita.
i can't wait to see him growing up.
How happy our lives are!
A ghost?!
it's me, Nobita-kun!
Oh! It's you, Doraemon.
Did you enjoy your time here?
Sure did...
Then it's about time we leave...
Go back?
Don't wanna. Everyone here is happy about me, after all.
I will grow up like this only.
But I don't think that's a good idea!
why not? I'm a genius, after all.
Everyone thinks I'll be a professor or even a minister...
It'll get worse eventually...
Liar!
Nobita-kun, you must put more effort...
rather than simply relying on Life Do-Over Machine.
I have no intention to go home.
It can't be helped.
Time TV!
Allow me to show you what happens in this timeline!
First grade, primary school!
Well done.
Gouda-kun!
Yes?
Oh, she's handing down the exam results.
Nobi-kun?
Yes?
So smart, full marks again..
Sure enough!
I am home!
Wanna see my marks card?
100 again? It's pretty obvious.
Oh, really?
1'm going out to play.
What about the study?
Too simple.
You have a point.
I should ask the teacher to skip the next 3 grades and promote him.
Nobita's here!
Nobita's here to rescue our team!
Nobita's here, the victory's gonna be ours.
Great!
Got!
I love you, Nobita-chan. You're great at studies, and sports.
I'm happy that I choose to redo my life!
Then, see what it is like in the 5 grade.
Nobita, you're trying to hide from me, you must have got 0 again.
Go and study harder!
Ok, I will study.
Why? What's going on here?!
You only have the intellect of a 2nd grader.
IQ has stopped.
How come?
Rewind to a little earlier time.
Let's see what happened today...
I wanna play too...!
Same as today's morning!
OK, I will kick it to you!
Come on!
Nothing has changed.
Same thing.
Haven't I seen you somewhere before?
Isn't it just the same?
Well, watch what happens next.
Hmm.. maybe I mistook you for someone else?
What are you doing there, Nobita?!
I'll kick it to you now...
Nobita! You are Nobi Nobita?
Yes. I am Nobita.
Remember me?
The educator from the genius academy...
who found you when you were 5 years old...
Ah, you're that educator mister from back then!
But I'm shocked to see you like this, Nobita-kun.
You're totally different than the last time I met you.
There's no shine in your eyes now.
No wonder I didn't recognized you.
What happened to the genius boy, I once knew?
Now; say do you still want to see more or grow up in this timeline?
No, I don't wanna see any more!
I'll go back, Doraemon!
Well, how did you liked it?
Did you understand now that...
you have to put in effort in order to succeed?
Sure did.
I'm gonna go study!
Great. That's the way, Nobita-kun.
Alright, I'm gonna study harder!
Then I'll invent a device that makes you smart...
...without ever having to study!
He still doesn't get it...